<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Gift.zip</string>
    <string name="gift_zip_email">giftzip.team@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="login_kakao">카카오톡으로 로그인</string>
    <string name="notice_select_image">사진을 등록해보세요.</string>
    <string name="write_emotion_hint">지금 이 감정을 기록해 보세요.</string>
    <string name="write_name_from">From.&#160;</string>
    <string name="write_name_to">To.&#160;</string>
    <string name="write_name_hint">이름</string>
    <string name="write_date_picker_finish">확인</string>
    <string name="home_taken_button_name">받은</string>
    <string name="home_given_button_name">보낸</string>
    <string name="taken_main_string">새로운 선물을\n받았나요?</string>
    <string name="given_main_string">새로운 선물을\n보냈나요?</string>
    <string name="home_write_button_name">기록하기</string>
    <string name="write_frame">프레임</string>
    <string name="frame_square">정사각형</string>
    <string name="frame_oval">원</string>
    <string name="frame_window">창문</string>
    <string name="share_insta_title">instagram에 게시</string>
    <string name="share_insta_story">스토리</string>
    <string name="share_insta_feed">피드</string>
    <string name="home_detail_button_name">선물함</string>
    <string name="setting_title">설정 · 문의</string>
    <string name="setting_service">서비스 설정</string>
    <string name="setting_current_version">현재버전 1.1.0</string>
    <string name="setting_using_current_version">최신 버전 사용 중</string>
    <string name="setting_using_old_version">업데이트 필요</string>
    <string name="setting_about_us">기프트집에 대해</string>
    <string name="setting_user_support">사용자 지원</string>
    <string name="setting_notice">공지사항</string>
    <string name="setting_question">앱 문의 · 건의</string>
    <string name="setting_app_info">앱 정보</string>
    <string name="setting_terms_of_use">서비스 이용약관</string>
    <string name="setting_opensource_license">오픈 소스 라이센스</string>
    <string name="setting_privacy_policy">개인정보 이용방침</string>
    <string name="setting_logout">로그아웃</string>
    <string name="about_us_producers">Gift.zip team\n기프트집을 만든 사람들</string>
    <string name="designer">Designer</string>
    <string name="backend">Backend Dev</string>
    <string name="ios">iOS Dev</string>
    <string name="android">Android Dev</string>
    <string name="jiyoung">jiyoung Kim</string>
    <string name="soyoung">soyoung Kim</string>
    <string name="jinna">jinna Choi</string>
    <string name="jihye">jihye  Park</string>
    <string name="jaeyong">jaeyong Lee</string>
    <string name="jeonghun">jeonghun Choi</string>
    <string name="junho">junho Seo</string>
    <string name="yujin">yujin Jin</string>
    <string name="about_us_qna">기프트집팀에 궁금한점?</string>
    <string name="qna_title">Gift.zip 문의/건의 메일</string>
    <string name="qna_content">- 정확한 문의 파악을 위해 아래 정보를 작성해주세요!\n\n\n1. 문의 내용:\n\n2. 기프트집(카카오) 메일계정:\n\n★ 문의 관련 스크린샷을 첨부하시면\n보다 정확하고 빠른 확인이 가능합니다.</string>
    <string name="notice_none_data_text1">아직 공지 사항이 없습니다</string>
    <string name="notice_none_data_text2">추후에 확인해주세요</string>
    <string name="terms_detail_title">기프트집 서비스 이용약관\n</string>
    <string name="opensource_detail_title">기프트집 사용 오픈소스</string>
    <string name="privacy_detail_title">기프트집 이용자\n개인정보 처리방침\n</string>
    <string name="share_notice_title">선물.zip이 보관됐어요\n저장하거나 공유해보세요</string>
    <string name="share_notice_sub_title">받은 마음은 널리널리 자랑하기</string>
    <string name="share_notice_save_image">저장이 완료되었습니다.</string>
    <string name="search_latest_searched">내가 찾아 봤던</string>
    <string name="search_latest_delete">지우기</string>
    <string name="search_category">지금 찾는 선물의 종류는</string>
    <string name="search_situation">선물을 주고 받았던 상황은</string>
    <string name="search_person">그동안 주고 받은 사람들은</string>
    <string name="category_mobile_coupon">모바일교환권</string>
    <string name="category_fashion">패션</string>
    <string name="category_cosmetic">화장품</string>
    <string name="category_food">식품</string>
    <string name="category_voucher">상품권</string>
    <string name="category_digital">디지털</string>
    <string name="category_sports">스포츠</string>
    <string name="category_baby">육아용품</string>
    <string name="category_pet">애견</string>
    <string name="category_living">리빙</string>
    <string name="category_culture">문화</string>
    <string name="search_etc">기타</string>
    <string name="situation_birthday">생일</string>
    <string name="situation_anniversary">기념일</string>
    <string name="situation_getJob">취업</string>
    <string name="situation_housewarming">집들이</string>
    <string name="situation_wedding">결혼</string>
    <string name="situation_study">학업</string>
    <string name="situation_holiday">명절</string>
    <string name="situation_cheer">응원</string>
    <string name="situation_apology">사과</string>
    <string name="situation_thanks">감사</string>
    <string name="situation_noReason">그냥</string>
    <string name="search_auto_textView_hint">이름, 내용 검색</string>
    <string name="search_none_text1">검색 결과가 없습니다</string>
    <string name="search_none_text2">다른 키워드로 검색해보세요.</string>
    <string name="search_error_text1">문제가 생겼어요</string>
    <string name="search_error_text2">잠시 후 다시 시도해보세요.</string>
    <string name="search_result_taken">받은 선물</string>
    <string name="search_result_given">보낸 선물</string>
    <string name="home_default_taken">아직 받은 선물이 없어요\n상단 버튼을 통해\n선물집을 만들어봐요</string>
    <string name="home_default_given">아직 보낸 선물이 없어요\n상단 버튼을 통해\n선물집을 만들어봐요</string>
    <string name="login_guide_title1">주고 받은\n선물을 기록해보세요</string>
    <string name="login_guide_detail1">선물 종류부터 감정, 원하는 스티커까지</string>
    <string name="login_guide_title2">친구에게 기록을\n공유해보세요</string>
    <string name="login_guide_title3">선물 기록을\n차곡차곡 모아보세요</string>
    <string name="detail_edit">수정하기</string>
    <string name="detail_delete">삭제하기</string>
    <string name="detail_share">공유하기</string>
    <string name="detail_cancel">취소</string>
    <string name="detail_notice_edit_success">수정이 완료되었습니다.</string>
    <string name="sort_latest">최신순</string>
    <string name="sort_past">과거순</string>
    <string name="sticker_update_scheduled">업데이트 예정</string>
    <string name="setting_terms_detail">"제1조 (목적)

본 약관은 회원(본 약관에 동의한 자를 말합니다. 이하 “회원”이라고 합니다.) 이 gift.zip(이하 “회사”라고 합니다.) 이 제공하는 gift.zip 앱 서비스(이하 “서비스”라고 합니다.)를 이용함에 있어 회사와 회원의 권리·의무 및 책임사항을 규정함을 목적으로 합니다.



제2조 (약관의 명시, 효력 및 개정)

1. 회사는 본 약관의 내용을 회원이 알 수 있도록 서비스 페이지 내에 항시 게시함으로써 이를 공지합니다.

2. 회사는 콘텐츠산업 진흥법, 정보통신망 이용촉진 및 정보보호 등 에 관한 법률, 약관의 규제에 관한 법률, 소비자기본법 등 관련 법령을 위배하지 않는 범위에서 본 약관을 개정할 수 있습니다.

3. 회사가 약관을 개정할 경우에는 개정약관 및 개정약관의 시행일자와 개정사유를 명시하여 그 시행일자 15일 전부터 시행일 이후 상당한 기간동안 본 서비스 페이지에 게시하며, 개정된 약관은 그 시행일에 효력이 발생합니다. 단, 개정 내용이 회원에게 불리한 경우에는 그 시행일자 30일 전부터 시행일 이후 상당한 기간 동안 본 서비스 페이지에 게시하거나 팝업화면을 게시하는 등 이용자가 충분히 인지할 수 있는 합리적으로 가능한 방법으로 공지하며, 개정된 약관은 그 시행일에 효력이 발생됩니다.

4. 회사가 전항에 따라 회원에게 통지하면서 공지일로부터 개정약관시행일까지 거부의사를 표시하지 아니하면 승인한 것으로 본다는 뜻을 명확하게 고지하였음에도 불구하고 회원의 거부의 의사표시가 없는 경우에는 변경된 약관에 동의한 것으로 봅니다. 회원이 개정약관에 동의하지 않을 경우 회원은 제14조 제1항의 규정에 따라 이용 계약을 해지할 수 있습니다.



제3조 (약관 동의 및 서비스 이용계약의 체결)

1. 회사와 회원 간의 서비스 이용계약은 이용자가 본 약관 내용에 대해 동의하고 서비스 이용신청을 하면 회사가 그 신청을 승낙함으로써 성립합니다.

2. 회사는 이용자가 서비스 회원가입 페이지의 "동의함" 버튼을 클릭하거나 이용자가 본 서비스의 이용을 시작한 경우 본 약관에 동의한 것으로 간주합니다.

3. 회사는 이용자가 필수사항 등을 성실히 입력하여 서비스 이용신청을 완료하였을 때에는 신청 내용을 확인한 후 지체 없이 이를 승낙하여야 합니다. 단, 회사는 아래 각 호에 해당하는 경우에는 승낙을 유보할 수 있습니다.

① 서비스의 설비용량에 현실적인 여유가 없는 경우
② 서비스를 제공하기에는 기술적으로 문제가 있다고 판단되는 경우

4. 본 서비스 이용계약은 회사가 신청절차 상에서 가입완료를 표시한 시점에 성립합니다.



제4조 (개인정보의 보호 및 관리)

1. 회사는 서비스를 제공하기 위하여 회원으로부터 서비스 이용에 필요한 개인정보를 수집할 수 있습니다.

2. 회사는 관련 법령이 정하는 바에 따라 회원의 개인정보를 보호하기 위해 노력하며, 회원의 개인정보의 보호 및 사용에 대해서는 회사가 별도로 고지하는 개인정보 처리방침을 적용합니다.

3. 회사는 회사의 귀책 없이 회원의 귀책사유로 인하여 회원의 정보가 노출된 경우 이에 대해서는 책임을 지지 않습니다.



제5조 (게시물의 관리 및 임시조치)

1. 서비스 내 모든 게시물 및 콘텐츠(테마)의 관리 권한 및 책임은 해당 게시물 및 콘텐츠를 게시한 회원에게 있습니다. 단 회원의 요청이 있거나 기타 회사가 서비스의 원활한 운영을 위하여 필요하다고 판단되는 경우, 회사는 게시물의 관리 등과 관련한 사항을 개선,지원하는 등의 활동을 할 수 있습니다.

2. 회사의 게시물 등이 관련 법령에 위반되는 내용을 포함하는 경우, 회사는 해당 관련 법령이나 적법한 고권리자의 요청에 따라 해당 게시물 등에 대한 게시중단 및 삭제 등의 조치를 취할 수 있습니다.

3. 회사는 게시물 등에 회사의 약관 및 서비스 운영정책에 위반되는 사유가 있는 것으로 확인된 경우, 운영정책에 따라 해당 게시물에 대해 조치를 취할 수 있습니다.

4. 정보통신망 이용촉진 및 정보보호 등에 관한 법률(이하 “정보통신망법”이라 합니다)의 규정에 의해 다른 회원의 공개된 게시물 등이 본인의 사생활을 침해하거나 명예를 훼손하는 등 권리를 침해 받은 회원 또는 제3자(이하 “삭제 등 신청인” 이라 합니다)는 그 침해사실을 소명하여 회사에 해당 게시물 등의 삭제 또는 반박 내용의 게재를 요청할 수 있습니다. 이 경우 회사는 해당 게시물 등의 권리침해 여부를 판단할 수 없거나 당사자 간의 다툼이 예상되는 경우 해당 게시물 등에 대한 접근을 임시적으로 차단하는 조치 (이하 '임시조치'라 합니다)를 최장 30일까지 취합니다.

5. 전항에 의해 본인의 게시물 등이 임시조치 된 회원(이하 “게시자”라 합니다)은 임시조치기간 중 회사에 해당 게시물 등을 복원해 줄 것을 요청(이하 “재 게시 청구”라 합니다)할 수 있으며, 회사는 임시조치 된 게시물의 명예훼손 등 판단에 대한 방송통신심의위원회 심의 요청에 대한 게시자 및 삭제 등 신청인의 동의가 있는 경우 게시자 및 삭제 등 신청인을 대리하여 이를 요청하고 동의가 없는 경우 회사가 이를 판단하여 게시물 등의 복원 여부를 결정합니다. 게시자의 재 게시 청구가 있는 경우 임시조치 기간 내에 방송통신심의위원회 또는 회사의 결정이 있으면 그 결정에 따르고 그 결정이 임시조치 기간 내에 있지 않은 경우 해당 게시물 등은 임시 조치 만료일 이후 복원됩니다. 재 게시 청구가 없는 경우 해당 게시물 등은 임시조치 기간 만료 이후 삭제됩니다.

6. 회사는 서비스 내에 게시된 게시물 등이 원저작자의 중대한 권리를 침해한다고 인정하는 경우 회원 또는 제3자의 신고가 없는 경우에도 임시조치(이하 “임의의 임시조치”라 합니다)를 취할 수 있습니다.

7. 회원의 게시물 등으로 인한 법률상 이익 침해를 근거로, 원저작자가 회원 또는 회사를 대상으로 하여 민·형사상의 법적 조치를 취하는 경우, 회사는 동 법적 조치의 결과인 법원의 확정판결이 있을 때까지 관련 게시물 등에 대한 접근을 잠정적으로 제한할 수 있습니다. 게시물 등의 접근 제한과 관련한 법적 조치의 소명, 법원의 확정 판결에 대한 소명 책임은 당사자가 부담합니다.



제6조 (회원의 의무)

1. 회원은 아래 각 호에 해당하는 행위를 하여서는 안됩니다.

• 회사의 서비스에 게시된 정보를 변경하거나 이용하여 영리 또는 비영리의 목적으로 복제·출판·방송 등에 사용하거나 제3자에게 제공하는 행위
• 회사가 제공하는 서비스를 이용하여 제3자에게 본인을 홍보할 기회를 제공하거나 제3자의 홍보를 대행하는 등의 방법으로 금전을 수수하거나 서비스를 이용할 권리를 양도하고 이를 대가로 금전을 수수하는 행위
• 회사 기타 제3자 혹은 원저작자의 명예를 훼손하거나 저작권을 침해하는 등의 권리를 침해하는 행위
• 다른 회원의 계정을 도용하여 부당하게 서비스를 이용하는 행위
• 외설 또는 폭력적인 메시지·화상·음성 등이 담긴 내용을 게시하거나 공공질서 또는 공서양속에 반하는 정보를 공개 또는 게시하는 행위
• 정보통신망법 등 관련 법령에 의하여 그 전송 또는 게시가 금지되는 정보(컴퓨터 프로그램 등)를 전송 게시하거나 청소년보호법에서 규정하는 청소년유해매체물을 게시하는 행위
• 회사의 직원이나 서비스의 관리자를 가장하거나 사칭하여 또는 타인의 명의를 도용하여 게시물 등을 작성하거나 이메일을 발송 하는 행위
• 컴퓨터 소프트웨어, 하드웨어, 전기통신 장비의 정상적인 가동을 방해 파괴할 목적으로 고안된 소프트웨어 바이러스, 기타 다른 컴퓨터 코드 파일 프로그램을 포함하고 있는 자료를 게시하거나 다른 회원에게 발송하는 행위
• 스토킹(stalking), 스팸성 댓글의 게재 등 다른 회원의 정상적인 서비스 이용을 방해하는 행위
• 다른 회원의 개인정보를 그 동의 없이 수집·저장·공개하는 행위 광고 또는 선전 등 영리 목적으로 서비스를 이용하는 행위
• 회사가 제공하는 소프트웨어 등을 개작하거나 리버스 엔지니어링, 디컴파일, 디스어셈블 하는 행위
• 본 약관 및 회사가 규정한 서비스 운영정책을 위반하는 행위

2. 회사는 회원이 전항 각 호의 행위를 하는 경우 해당 게시물 등을 삭제 또는 임시 조치할 수 있고 회원의 서비스 이용을 제한하거나 그 사유가 중대한 경우 일방적으로 본 계약을 해지할 수 있습니다.

3. 회원이 본 조 제2항 각 호의 행위를 함으로써 회사에 손해가 발생한 경우, 회사는 해당 회원에 대해 손해배상을 청구할 수 있습니다.

4. 본 서비스 내에서 회사의 관여 없이 회원 간 이루어지는 일체의 행위(거래행위 포함)와 관련하여 발생하는 모든 의무와 책임은 해당 회원에게 있으며, 회사는 그 내용에 대하여 책임을 지지 않습니다.



제7조 (서비스 이용의 제한 및 중지)

1. 회사는 아래 각 호에 해당하는 사유가 발생한 경우에는 회원의 서비스 이용을 제한하거나 중지시킬 수 있습니다.

• 회원이 회사의 서비스 운영을 고의 또는 과실로 방해하는 경우
• 회원이 제6조의 의무를 위반한 경우
• 기타 중대한 사유로 인하여 회사가 해당 회원에 대해 서비스 제공을 지속하는 것이 상당하지 않다고 판단되는 경우

2. 회사는 전항의 규정에 의하여 서비스의 이용을 제한하거나 중지한 때에는 그 사유 및 제한 기간 등을 회원에게 알립니다.



제8조 (계정의 관리책임)

회원은 본인의 계정 관리에 대한 책임을 부담하며, 본인 계정을 제3 자가 무단 이용하는 등 회원의 귀책사유로 인해 발생하는 모든 불이익에 대한 책임을 부담합니다.



제9조(양도금지)

회원의 서비스 받을 권리는 이를 양도 내지 증여의 대상으로 하거나 질권의 목적으로 활용할 수 없습니다.



제 10 조 (이용계약의 해지)

1. 회원이 본 서비스 이용계약을 해지하고자 하는 때에는 회사가 제공하는 서비스 내의 회원탈퇴 기능을 이용하여 탈퇴를 요청할 수 있습니다. 회사는 탈퇴를 요청한 시점에서 불가피한 사정이 없는한 즉시 탈퇴요청을 처리합니다.

2. 본 이용 계약이 해지된 경우 회원의 게시물 등은 삭제됩니다. 단, 서비스 운영에 필요한 테마 등은 남을 수 있습니다.



제 11 조 (면책조항)

1. 회사는 다음 각 호의 사유로 서비스를 제공할 수 없는 경우 이로 인하여 회원에게 발생한 손해에 대해서는 책임을 부담하지 않습니다.

• 천재지변 또는 이에 준하는 불가항력의 상태가 있는 경우
• 제3자의 고의적인 서비스 방해가 있는 경우
• 회원의 귀책사유로 서비스 이용에 장애가 발생한 경우
• 제1호 내지 제3호를 제외한 기타 회사의 고의·과실이 없는 사유로 서비스를 제공하는 것이 어려운 경우

2. 회사는 회원이 작성하여 서비스에 게재된 정보 및 자료의 신뢰도나 정확성 등에 대해서는 보증을 하지 않으며 이로 인해 발생한 회원의 손해에 대하여는 책임을 부담하지 아니합니다.



제 12 조 (회원에 대한 통지)

회사가 회원에 대한 통지를 하는 경우, 본 약관에 별도 규정이 없는한 회원이 회사에 제공한 이메일 주소로 통지할 수 있습니다.



제 13 조 (약관의 해석)

본 약관에 명시되지 않은 사항에 대해서는 회사와 회원 간 합의하여 결정하고, 합의가 되지 않는 경우 관련 법령 또는 상관례에 따릅니다.



제 14 조 (준거법 및 재판관할)

1. 본 약관은 대한민국법에 의하여 규정되고 이행되며, 회사와 회원간에 제기된 소송에는 대한민국법을 적용합니다.

2. 서비스 이용과 관련하여 회사와 회원 간에 발생한 분쟁은 서울중앙지방법원 또는 민사소송법 상의 관할법원에 제기합니다.

본 약관은 2021년 2월 20일부터 적용됩니다.


        "</string>
    <string name="setting_privacy_detail">"기프트집 서비스 제작자(팀)은 이용자의 개인정보를 보호하고 이와 관련된 고충을 신속하고 원활하게 처리할 수 있도록 다음과 같이 개인정보 처리방침을 수립, 공개합니다.


○ 본 방침은부터 2021년 2월 20일부터 시행됩니다.

1. 개인정보의 처리 목적
‘Gift.zip’는 개인정보를 다음의 목적을 위해 처리합니다. 처리한 개인정보는 다음의 목적이외의 용도로는 사용되지 않으며 이용 목적이 변경될 시에는 사전 동의를 구할 예정입니다.

가. 홈페이지 회원가입 및 관리
회원 가입의사 확인, 회원제 서비스 제공에 따른 본인 식별·인증, 회원자격 유지·관리, 제한적 본인확인제 시행에 따른 본인 확인, 서비스 부정이용 방지, 고충처리 등을 목적으로 개인정보를 처리 합니다.


2. 개인정보 파일 현황
· 1. 개인정보 파일명 : Gift.zip
· 개인정보 항목 : 카카오 로그인ID
· 수집방법 : 사용자가 입력
· 보유근거 : 단순 어플이용
· 보유기간 : 회원 가입 시 부터 회원 탈퇴 시
· 관련법령 : 신용정보의 수집/처리 및 이용 등에 관한 기록 : 3년


3. 개인정보의 처리 및 보유 기간
①'Gift.zip'은 법령에 따른 개인정보 보유·이용기간 또는 정보 주체로부터 개인정보를 수집시에 동의 받은 개인정보 보유, 이용 기간 내에서 개인정보를 처리,보유합니다.
②각각의 개인정보 처리 및 보유 기간은 다음과 같습니다.


4. 개인정보의 제3자 제공에 관한 사항
①'Gift.zip'은 정보주체의 동의, 법률의 특별한 규정 등 개인정보보호법 제17조 및 제18조에 해당하는 경우에만 개인정보를 제3자에게 제공합니다.
②'Gift.zip’은 다음과 같이 개인정보를 제3자에게 제공하고 있습니다.


5. 개인정보처리 위탁
①'Gift.zip’은 원활한 개인정보 업무처리를 위하여 다음과 같이 개인정보 처리업무를 위탁하고 있습니다.
②'Gift.zip’은 위탁계약 체결시 개인정보 보호법 제25조에 따라 위탁업무 수행목적 외 개인정보 처리금지, 기술적․관리적 보호조치, 재위탁 제한, 수탁자에 대한 관리․감독, 손해배상 등 책임에 관한 사항을 계약서 등 문서에 명시하고, 수탁자가 개인정보를 안전하게 처리하는지를 감독하고 있습니다.
③위탁업무의 내용이나 수탁자가 변경될 경우에는 지체없이 본 개인정보 처리방침을 통하여 공개하도록 하겠습니다.


6. 정보주체와 법정대리인의 권리·의무 및 그 행사방법
이용자는 개인정보주체로써 다음과 같은 권리를 행사할 수
있습니다.

① 정보주체는 Gift.zip에 대해 언제든지 개인정보 열람,정정,삭제, 처리정지 요구 등의 권리를 행사할 수 있습니다.
② 제1항에 따른 권리 행사는 Gift.zip에 대해 개인정보 보호법 시행령 제41조제1항에 따라 서면, 전자우편, 모사전송(FAX) 등을 통하여 하실 수 있으며 ‘Gift.zip’는이에 대해 지체 없이 조치하겠습니다.
③ 제1항에 따른 권리 행사는 정보주체의 법정대리인이나 위임을 받은 자 등 대리인을 통하여 하실 수 있습니다. 이 경우 개인정보보호법 시행규칙 별지 제11호 서식에 따른 위임장을 제출하셔야합니다.
④ 개인정보 열람 및 처리정지 요구는 개인정보보호법 제35조 제5 항, 제37조 제2항에 의하여 정보주체의 권리가 제한 될 수 있습니다.
⑤ 개인정보의 정정 및 삭제 요구는 다른 법령에서 그 개인정보가 수집 대상으로 명시되어 있는 경우에는 그 삭제를 요구할 수 없습니다.
⑥ ‘Gift.zip’는 정보주체 권리에 따른 열람의 요구, 정정·삭제의 요구, 처리정지의 요구 시 열람 등 요구를 한 자가 본인이거나 정당한 대리인인지를 확인합니다.


7. 처리하는 개인정보의 항목 작성
① ‘Gift.zip’은 다음의 개인정보 항목을 처리하고 있습니다.

· &lt;홈페이지 회원가입 및 관리&gt;
· 필수항목 : 카카오 로그인ID


8. 개인정보의 파기
‘Gift.zip’은 원칙적으로 개인정보 처리 목적이 달성된 경우에는 지체없이 해당 개인정보를 파기합니다. 파기의 절차, 기한 및 방법은 다음과 같습니다.

- 파기절차
이용자가 입력한 정보는 목적 달성 후 별도의 DB에 옮겨져(종이의 경우 별도의 서류) 내부 방침 및 기타 관련 법령에 따라 일정기간 저장된 후 혹은 즉시 파기됩니다. 이 때, DB로 옮겨진 개인정보는 법률에 의한 경우가 아니고서는 다른 목적으로 이용되지 않습니다.

-파기기한
이용자의 개인정보는 개인정보의 보유기간이 경과된 경우에는 보유기간의 종료일로부터 5일 이내에, 개인정보의 처리 목적 달성, 해당 서비스의 폐지, 사업의 종료 등 그 개인정보가 불필요하게 되었을 때에는 개인정보의 처리가 불필요한 것으로 인정되는 날로부터 5일 이내에 그 개인정보를 파기합니다.

- 파기방법
전자적 파일 형태의 정보는 기록을 재생할 수 없는 기술적 방법을 사용합니다


9. 개인정보 자동 수집 장치의 설치•운영 및 거부에 관한 사항
‘Gift.zip’은 정보주체의 이용정보를 저장하고 수시로 불러오는 ‘쿠키’를 사용하지 않습니다.


10. 개인정보 보호책임자 작성
① ‘Gift.zip’은(는) 개인정보 처리에 관한 업무를 총괄해서 책임지고, 개인정보 처리와 관련한 정보주체의 불만처리 및 피해구제 등을 위하여 아래와 같이 개인정보 관리자를 지정하고 있습니다.
· 개인정보 관리자
· 연락처 : 010.8024.5602, smile5602@naver.com,
※ 개인정보 보호 담당부서로 연결됩니다.

② 정보주체께서는 ‘Gift.zip’의 서비스(또는 사업)을 이용하시면서 발생한 모든 개인정보 보호 관련 문의, 불만처리, 피해구제 등에 관한 사항을 개인정보 보호책임자 및 담당부서로 문의하실 수 있습니다. ‘Gift.zip’은 정보주체의 문의에 대해 지체 없이 답변 및 처리해드릴 것입니다.


11. 개인정보 처리방침 변경
① 이 개인정보처리방침은 시행일로부터 적용되며, 법령 및 방침에 따른 변경내용의 추가, 삭제 및 정정이 있는 경우에는 변경사항의 시행 7일 전부터 공지사항을 통하여 고지할 것입니다.


12. 개인정보의 안전성 확보 조치 'Gift.zip’은 개인정보보호
법 제29조에 따라 다음과 같이 안전성 확보에 필요한
기술적/관리적 및 물리적 조치를 하고 있습니다.

1. 개인정보 취급 직원의 최소화 및 교육
개인정보를 취급하는 직원을 지정하고 담당자에 한정시켜 최소화하여 개인정보를 관리하는 대책을 시행하고 있습니다.
2. 개인정보에 대한 접근 제한
개인정보를 처리하는 데이터베이스시스템에 대한 접근권한의 부여,변경,말소를 통하여 개인정보에 대한 접근통제를 위하여 필요한 조치를 하고 있으며 침입차단시스템을 이용하여 외부로부터의 무단 접근을 통제하고 있습니다.
3. 비인가자에 대한 출입 통제
개인정보를 보관하고 있는 물리적 보관 장소를 별도로 두고 이에 대해 출입통제 절차를 수립, 운영하고 있습니다.

        "</string>

    <string name="coroutine_opensource_detail">"The MIT License (MIT)

Copyright © 2016 Parker Moore

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in
all copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN
THE SOFTWARE."</string>

    <string name="koin_opensource_detail">"Apache License
Version 2.0, January 2004
[http://www.apache.org/licenses/](http://www.apache.org/licenses/)

TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USE, REPRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION

1. Definitions.
1. Grant of Copyright License. Subject to the terms and conditions of
this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,
worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable
copyright license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of,
publicly display, publicly perform, sublicense, and distribute the
Work and such Derivative Works in Source or Object form.
1. Grant of Patent License. Subject to the terms and conditions of
this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,
worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable
(except as stated in this section) patent license to make, have made,
use, offer to sell, sell, import, and otherwise transfer the Work,
where such license applies only to those patent claims licensable
by such Contributor that are necessarily infringed by their
Contribution(s) alone or by combination of their Contribution(s)
with the Work to which such Contribution(s) was submitted. If You
institute patent litigation against any entity (including a
cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that the Work
or a Contribution incorporated within the Work constitutes direct
or contributory patent infringement, then any patent licenses
granted to You under this License for that Work shall terminate
as of the date such litigation is filed.
1. Redistribution. You may reproduce and distribute copies of the
Work or Derivative Works thereof in any medium, with or without
modifications, and in Source or Object form, provided that You
meet the following conditions:
1. Submission of Contributions. Unless You explicitly state otherwise,
any Contribution intentionally submitted for inclusion in the Work
by You to the Licensor shall be under the terms and conditions of
this License, without any additional terms or conditions.
Notwithstanding the above, nothing herein shall supersede or modify
the terms of any separate license agreement you may have executed
with Licensor regarding such Contributions.
1. Trademarks. This License does not grant permission to use the trade
names, trademarks, service marks, or product names of the Licensor,
except as required for reasonable and customary use in describing the
origin of the Work and reproducing the content of the NOTICE file.
1. Disclaimer of Warranty. Unless required by applicable law or
agreed to in writing, Licensor provides the Work (and each
Contributor provides its Contributions) on an "AS IS" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or
implied, including, without limitation, any warranties or conditions
of TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, or FITNESS FOR A
PARTICULAR PURPOSE. You are solely responsible for determining the
appropriateness of using or redistributing the Work and assume any
risks associated with Your exercise of permissions under this License.
1. Limitation of Liability. In no event and under no legal theory,
whether in tort (including negligence), contract, or otherwise,
unless required by applicable law (such as deliberate and grossly
negligent acts) or agreed to in writing, shall any Contributor be
liable to You for damages, including any direct, indirect, special,
incidental, or consequential damages of any character arising as a
result of this License or out of the use or inability to use the
Work (including but not limited to damages for loss of goodwill,
work stoppage, computer failure or malfunction, or any and all
other commercial damages or losses), even if such Contributor
has been advised of the possibility of such damages.
1. Accepting Warranty or Additional Liability. While redistributing
the Work or Derivative Works thereof, You may choose to offer,
and charge a fee for, acceptance of support, warranty, indemnity,
or other liability obligations and/or rights consistent with this
License. However, in accepting such obligations, You may act only
on Your own behalf and on Your sole responsibility, not on behalf
of any other Contributor, and only if You agree to indemnify,
defend, and hold each Contributor harmless for any liability
incurred by, or claims asserted against, such Contributor by reason
of your accepting any such warranty or additional liability.

END OF TERMS AND CONDITIONS

APPENDIX: How to apply the Apache License to your work.

```
  To apply the Apache License to your work, attach the following
  boilerplate notice, with the fields enclosed by brackets "{}"
  replaced with your own identifying information. (Don't include
  the brackets!)  The text should be enclosed in the appropriate
  comment syntax for the file format. We also recommend that a
  file or class name and description of purpose be included on the
  same "printed page" as the copyright notice for easier
  identification within third-party archives.

```

Copyright 2017 Arnaud GIULIANI, Laurent BARESSE

Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at

```
   &lt;http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0&gt;

```

Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
limitations under the License."</string>

    <string name="retrofit_opensource_detail">"Copyright 2013 Square, Inc.

Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at

   http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
limitations under the License."</string>
    
    <string name="gson_opensource_detail">"Copyright 2008 Google Inc.

Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at

    http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
limitations under the License."</string>
    
    <string name="glide_opensource_detail">"License for everything not in third_party and not otherwise marked:

Copyright 2014 Google, Inc. All rights reserved.

Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are
permitted provided that the following conditions are met:

1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of
conditions and the following disclaimer.
1. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list
of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials
provided with the distribution.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY GOOGLE, INC. ``AS IS'' AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED
WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL GOOGLE, INC. OR
CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR
CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR
SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON
ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING
NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF
ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.

## The views and conclusions contained in the software and documentation are those of the
authors and should not be interpreted as representing official policies, either expressed
or implied, of Google, Inc.

License for third_party/disklrucache:

Copyright 2012 Jake Wharton
Copyright 2011 The Android Open Source Project

Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at

[http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0](http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0)

## Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
limitations under the License.

License for third_party/gif_decoder:

Copyright © 2013 Xcellent Creations, Inc.

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining
a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the
"Software"), to deal in the Software without restriction, including
without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish,
distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to
permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to
the following conditions:

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be
included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.

## THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND,
EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF
MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND
NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE
LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION
OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION
WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.

License for third_party/gif_encoder/AnimatedGifEncoder.java and
third_party/gif_encoder/LZWEncoder.java:

No copyright asserted on the source code of this class. May be used for any
purpose, however, refer to the Unisys LZW patent for restrictions on use of
the associated LZWEncoder class. Please forward any corrections to
[kweiner@fmsware.com](mailto:kweiner@fmsware.com).

---

License for third_party/gif_encoder/NeuQuant.java

Copyright © 1994 Anthony Dekker

NEUQUANT Neural-Net quantization algorithm by Anthony Dekker, 1994. See
"Kohonen neural networks for optimal colour quantization" in "Network:
Computation in Neural Systems" Vol. 5 (1994) pp 351-367. for a discussion of
the algorithm.

Any party obtaining a copy of these files from the author, directly or
indirectly, is granted, free of charge, a full and unrestricted irrevocable,
world-wide, paid up, royalty-free, nonexclusive right and license to deal in
this software and documentation files (the "Software"), including without
limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute,
sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons who
receive copies from any such party to do so, with the only requirement being
that this copyright notice remain intact."</string>
    
    <string name="cropper_opensource_detail">"Originally forked from edmodo/cropper.

Copyright 2016, Arthur Teplitzki, 2013, Edmodo, Inc.

Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); you may not use this work except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License in the LICENSE file, or at:

[http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0](http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0)

Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License."</string>

    <string name="stickerview_opensource_detail">"Copyright 2016 wuapnjie

Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at

[http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0](http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0)

Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
limitations under the License."</string>

    <string name="circleIndicator_opensource_detail">"Apache License
Version 2.0, January 2004
[http://www.apache.org/licenses/](http://www.apache.org/licenses/)

TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USE, REPRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION

1. Definitions.
1. Grant of Copyright License. Subject to the terms and conditions of
this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,
worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable
copyright license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of,
publicly display, publicly perform, sublicense, and distribute the
Work and such Derivative Works in Source or Object form.
1. Grant of Patent License. Subject to the terms and conditions of
this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,
worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable
(except as stated in this section) patent license to make, have made,
use, offer to sell, sell, import, and otherwise transfer the Work,
where such license applies only to those patent claims licensable
by such Contributor that are necessarily infringed by their
Contribution(s) alone or by combination of their Contribution(s)
with the Work to which such Contribution(s) was submitted. If You
institute patent litigation against any entity (including a
cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that the Work
or a Contribution incorporated within the Work constitutes direct
or contributory patent infringement, then any patent licenses
granted to You under this License for that Work shall terminate
as of the date such litigation is filed.
1. Redistribution. You may reproduce and distribute copies of the
Work or Derivative Works thereof in any medium, with or without
modifications, and in Source or Object form, provided that You
meet the following conditions:
1. Submission of Contributions. Unless You explicitly state otherwise,
any Contribution intentionally submitted for inclusion in the Work
by You to the Licensor shall be under the terms and conditions of
this License, without any additional terms or conditions.
Notwithstanding the above, nothing herein shall supersede or modify
the terms of any separate license agreement you may have executed
with Licensor regarding such Contributions.
1. Trademarks. This License does not grant permission to use the trade
names, trademarks, service marks, or product names of the Licensor,
except as required for reasonable and customary use in describing the
origin of the Work and reproducing the content of the NOTICE file.
1. Disclaimer of Warranty. Unless required by applicable law or
agreed to in writing, Licensor provides the Work (and each
Contributor provides its Contributions) on an "AS IS" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or
implied, including, without limitation, any warranties or conditions
of TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, or FITNESS FOR A
PARTICULAR PURPOSE. You are solely responsible for determining the
appropriateness of using or redistributing the Work and assume any
risks associated with Your exercise of permissions under this License.
1. Limitation of Liability. In no event and under no legal theory,
whether in tort (including negligence), contract, or otherwise,
unless required by applicable law (such as deliberate and grossly
negligent acts) or agreed to in writing, shall any Contributor be
liable to You for damages, including any direct, indirect, special,
incidental, or consequential damages of any character arising as a
result of this License or out of the use or inability to use the
Work (including but not limited to damages for loss of goodwill,
work stoppage, computer failure or malfunction, or any and all
other commercial damages or losses), even if such Contributor
has been advised of the possibility of such damages.
1. Accepting Warranty or Additional Liability. While redistributing
the Work or Derivative Works thereof, You may choose to offer,
and charge a fee for, acceptance of support, warranty, indemnity,
or other liability obligations and/or rights consistent with this
License. However, in accepting such obligations, You may act only
on Your own behalf and on Your sole responsibility, not on behalf
of any other Contributor, and only if You agree to indemnify,
defend, and hold each Contributor harmless for any liability
incurred by, or claims asserted against, such Contributor by reason
of your accepting any such warranty or additional liability.

END OF TERMS AND CONDITIONS

APPENDIX: How to apply the Apache License to your work.

```
  To apply the Apache License to your work, attach the following
  boilerplate notice, with the fields enclosed by brackets "[]"
  replaced with your own identifying information. (Don't include
  the brackets!)  The text should be enclosed in the appropriate
  comment syntax for the file format. We also recommend that a
  file or class name and description of purpose be included on the
  same "printed page" as the copyright notice for easier
  identification within third-party archives.

```

Copyright [yyyy] [name of copyright owner]

Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at

```
   &lt;http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0&gt;

```

Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
limitations under the License."</string>

    <string name="kakaoSDK_opensource_detail">"Copyright 2019 Kakao Corp.

Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at

   http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
limitations under the License."</string>

</resources>